Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[snorts] Heat. HEAT. HEAT.
HEAT.
Heat up here.
Heat
up here.
Heat. [music]
Heat.
Keep coming back. Nice and slow. Watch
your right side.
All right. Easy now. And stop.
Alto
heat.
Watch the alignment. KEEP IT STEADY.
>> WE HAVE CONTACT. Thumbs up on this side.
Confirmed. Set the brakes.
This connection looks solid now.
>> Yeah, the angle is correct.
Thumbs up on the rear alignment.
Clear to lift. All clear below.
>> ROGER THAT. CLEAR TO HOIST. Hoisting the
load.
Amidst the cold steel and industrial
lights, a seemingly dormant symbol
begins its journey of revival. Layers of
old paint peel away like memory being
raised, revealing the enduring strength
of metal and human hands. Each screw is
tightened not just with force, but with
respect for history. Steam, oil, and the
metallic clang resonate like the
familiar breath of the past. Each small
detail gradually finds its place. The
blue returns the
The alignment looks good. Yeah, the
paint finish is perfect. We did it.
Lower it slowly. Watch the left side.
>> Clear on this side. Keep it coming.
Heat. Heat.
According
to this diagram, the clearance should be
clearly 05.
>> We'll need the specialized gauge for
that reading.
Heat
up here.
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat. HEAT.
HEAT. HEAT.
HEAT.
TEDDY, watch the balance. Now increase
pressure slowly on Jack 4.
Heat up here.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
HEAT.
I think we finally nailed it.
>> Yeah. Smooth finish. Well done.
Heat.
All right, easy. Now bring it down
slowly on my marks. Watch the clearance.
A little higher on your side.
>> Got it. Is that flush?
>> Almost. [sighs and gasps]
[panting]
Keep it coming down steady. Just a
millimeter left.
Okay. Set it down gently.
The finest engine we've ever built.
>> Indeed. The paintwork is [music]
flawless.
The alignment on the front coupling
looks good. Yes, but check the paint
near the running board. There's a slight
imperfection here.
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat.
Heat.
>> [music]
>> How does that look on your end? Almost
there. Bring it down just a touch more.
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Red
identity.
Smiles are painted not just with pain
but with faith. Until the light reflects
off the completed machine body, the
space falls silent and before us is not
a restored locomotive but a complete
connection between memory,
craftsmanship,
ready to continue its story.
Heat.
[music]